Before we go any further, I need to
jump in here. Catherine has already said that
the refresh button is for debugging only, but
let's look at why. In real life, you
should always seek to eliminate the refresh button
from your app. A good app should work
like a good butler, giving you what you want before you even have to ask for
it.
Much like the Save button, it's a relic of a
bygone age. That's the best a reassuring safety blanket for those
of us who grew up with floppy disks. With the ability
to run background tasks or send messages directly from the server
to our app, there's really no reason to force users
to manually hit refresh. But the app is up to date
and sync with the cloud should be a given. But like
we said, this is for debugging, so like print line it's
acceptable for this particular purpose. Let's also take a look at
our background threading model, which of the following is potential an issue?